vinted.com 2017-03-10

# Vinted Inc. Privacy Policy

**Date of last revision: September 27, 2016**

Vinted Inc. (“Vinted”) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information. We want to share with you how we treat personal information about you that we receive in connection with your use of our website and mobile applications (collectively, the “Site”).

Also, please bear in mind that your use of this Site is governed by the [Terms and Conditions](https://www.vinted.com/terms-and-conditions) posted on the Site. Any capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning set forth in the Terms and Conditions. As noted in those Terms and Conditions, although we operate internationally, Vinted Inc. is a company organized under the laws of Delaware. The servers that host this Site are located in the United States, and any personal details you provide to us will be processed by Vinted in the United States. Vinted expressly excludes any representation or warranty, express or implied, with respect to the information available on this Site. Vinted makes no representation about any third-party websites that may be accessed via links from this Site. By using this Site, you agree that the laws of California, without regard to its conflict of laws principles, will govern all matters between you and Vinted with respect to your use of this Site.  

**Information We Collect**

  * Information You Provide

We collect your personal information if you voluntarily submit the information to us for such purposes as registering for the use of certain services, completion of surveys, submitting applications for employment, product or service purchases, or requests for information or services. For example, sections of this Site (including certain restricted portions) may allow you to submit personal information (referred to for convenience as “Registration Pages”), including your name, address, email address, phone number(s), account information and any other information that you decide to provide us with, either directly or via third-party services (for example, Facebook Connect). To protect your security and privacy, we require that you (as opposed to a third party on your behalf) enter the personal information that we collect and that the information be current, although Vinted disclaims any legal duty to verify the accuracy of any personal data that you provide to Vinted.

  * Location Information

You may provide information about your location, including your address, to us on our Site’s Registration Pages. If you post items for sale, we may use that information to tell other users, including potential buyers, your approximate distance away from them (but not your specific address). Similarly, when you review items for sale, we may use information that you have provided to us to give you an approximate distance between you and the seller. We may also collect and use current location information from your mobile device to do the same, but will ask you to allow us to collect such information, before we do so.

  * Automated Information Collection

We may automatically collect certain information when you visit our Site, such as your IP address; details about your browser, operating system and device/hardware; your location, if available; the URL that referred you to our website; your activities on our Site; and other logging information, including the date and time of your visit. We may use a variety of technologies for such data collection, including web logs, web beacons, clear GIFs, cookies and others.

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**

Like many websites, our Site uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer or mobile device’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by Vinted Users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Services and then close your browser. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site and the Site’s functionality may be limited. Please note that linked third-party websites may also use cookies. We cannot control the use of cookies by these third-party websites. For example, when you link from this Site to a third-party website, that website may have the ability to recognize that you have come from our Website by using cookies. If you have any questions about how third-party websites use cookies, you should contact such third parties directly. We may also employ software technology known as “web beacons” or “clear GIFs” which helps us keep track of what content on our Site is effective. Web beacons are small graphics with a unique identifier that are used to track the online movements of Internet users. Web beacons are embedded in the web pages you review, so they are not stored on your hard drive. The web beacons we use do not track or collect any personally identifiable information about you and they are in no way linked to your personally identifiable information.

**Analytics Services, Targeted Ads & Do-Not-Track**

We may also use third-party analytics services, including Google Analytics, and these services may track details about your online activities over time and across different websites, in addition to our Site. These services help us to improve our Site and operations. These services may also allow others to provide you with targeted ads or content that you may be interested in based on your online activities. You can learn more about Google Analytics and your choices[ here](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). If you would like to learn more about targeted ads and consumer choice, you may wish to visit the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance.

We do not respond to, or take any specific action in connection with the receipt of, Do-Not-Track signals or other similar mechanisms regarding the collection of information about an individual’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services.

**Accessing & Updating Your Information**

You are free to access the personal information we have on file by contacting our Customer Service department using our [contact form](https://www.vinted.com//help/new). In addition, at any time you can request that we modify or delete your personal information by contacting the team through our contact forum with the words “UPDATE MY INFORMATION” in body of your message. Please be aware that, to protect your security and privacy, Vinted may take reasonable steps to verify your identity prior to making changes to your personal information. 

**How We Use the Information We Collect and Who We Share It With**

Unless otherwise specified herein, Vinted reserves the right to compile, save, use within the scope of our activities, and analyze any and all data about you (contact and personal data, usage history, etc.) that we collect from you through the Site. We use the personal information about you that you provide to us for our internal purposes such as responding to your requests for information or materials, delivering newsletters to you, contacting you, assessing your application for a position with Vinted and entities related to Vinted, processing and completing orders, processing your payment, administering your account, and administering and developing our business relationship with you or the company you represent. We also use your personal information to communicate with you, such as, for example, to provide you with administrative communications regarding your account, newsletters, press releases, or information relating to products, offers, or programs that may be of interest to you.

We may share the personal information about you that you provide to us with trusted companies we have hired to provide services for us, such as sending out our newsletters, fulfilling orders you may submit, or collecting and processing information on our behalf. These companies – our vendors – are contractually bound to use personal information that we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide.

We may share your personal information to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoena, government request or other legal process. And, we may also share personal information with others, including law enforcement, to protect our Site and to enforce our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.vinted.com/terms-and-conditions). 

We may also share your personal information in the event that the business of Vinted is transferred to another entity by way of merger, sale of the company’s assets, or otherwise.

We may share your information with Vinted related entities and selected third parties so that they may provide you with or contact you regarding information and materials that may be of interest to you. Please refer to the section below on Opting In and Out.

We may also collect and group demographic and preferences information, responses to surveys and other personal information that we collect from you (as described in Information We Collect) into an aggregate, non-personally identifiable form for disclosure to our existing or potential business partners, affiliates, sponsors or other third parties. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors to the Site.

**Children’s Information and COPPA**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. The content of our Site and the products and services available are not intended for, or directed to, children. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access our website at any time or in any manner. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, please [contact us](https://www.vinted.com//help/new) and we will remove this information from our files. We recommend that parents and legal guardians monitor their children’s use of the Internet and instruct them never to provide personal information without their explicit consent. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

**Opting In and Out**

When you submit personal information to us through the Registration Pages on this Site, Vinted, Vinted related entities, and or selected third parties may use this information to communicate with you regarding the Services or to tell you about service we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, any marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please [contact us](https://www.vinted.com//help/new). Note that as a user of our service you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the service.

**Links to Other Sites and Site Accounts**

For your convenience, the Vinted Site may from time to time include links to third-party websites and online services whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ and services’ privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Site Accounts are pages on certain websites (for example, the Vinted page on Facebook), where the same information, as in our Site, is provided, because Vinted is the editor of both our Site and the Site Accounts. The Terms and Conditions, this Privacy Policy and other applicable rules published on our Site are binding on and apply to the Users and Visitors of Site Accounts. Users and Visitors should carefully read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of websites that host these Site Accounts, over which Vinted has no control. Vinted has Site Accounts on the following websites: Facebook, Google+, Twitter, Pinterest, YouTube, and other social networks. 

**Security of Information and Disclosures**

Vinted uses industry standard security measures to safeguard information concerning, and submitted by you. Despite the security measures employed by Vinted, you should be aware that it is impossible to guarantee absolute security with respect to information sent through the Internet.

Vinted will, to the extent possible, control your personal information, and, except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties. Although we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of your personal information, if required by law, we reserve the right to disclose such information without first obtaining your consent.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

The Site and Services may change from time to time. As a result, it may be necessary for Vinted to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. Vinted reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. We ask that you please review the Privacy Policy periodically, and especially before you provide personal information. This Policy was last updated on the Effective Date indicated above. Your continued use of this Site subsequent to any modification of this Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy. If any term or provision of this Privacy Policy shall be found to be invalid, illegal or otherwise unenforceable, such finding shall not affect the other terms or provisions of this Privacy Policy, or the whole of this Privacy Policy, but such term or provision shall be deemed modified to the extent necessary to render such term or provision enforceable, and the rights and obligations of you and Vinted shall be construed and enforced accordingly, preserving to the fullest permissible extent the intent and agreements set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions or concerns relating to this Privacy Policy, please contact us by clicking [here](https://www.vinted.com//help) or using the information below:

**PO BOX 210640    
San Francisco, CA, 94121**
